Hi, I'm Emily Larew continuing on with our intermediate hip hop combination.
We're on the third count of eight, counts one through four where we're going to hit the floor and then pop it.
Alright?
So we have just finished stepping out on one with our right foot and our left arm is in front.
We're then going to step on our left foot on one, one, alright?
We're going to pop it right here and two.
So your hands come in your chest because you're popping your chest out.
Releasing the lower back and popping it back in.
Alright?
So we just did this on eight.
We go, one, and two.
Make sure you straighten your knees, huge pop O.k?
and also if you can see I'm stepping, leaning towards my leg that I'm stepping on.
O.k?
So we did here on eight.
We will one, and two.
Now I want you to slap your legs as your arms come back.
You're going to release your upper back this time and come down on four.
O.k?
Make sure that as you slap the floor, your knees are bent.
Alright?
So we have here on eight.
We go one and two, three, four.
Good!
Try a little faster.
Nice job!
Don't be shy with that slapping the floor, just get it.
Ready?
Here we go, five, six, seven, eight.
One and two, three, four.
Good!
Let's try backing up now and we can add it all together.
Ready?
Here we go, hold four.
We've got one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
One and two, three, four, five and six, seven, eight and one, two, three and four, five, six and seven eight.
One and two, three, four.
Good!
That was our hit the floor and pop for intermediate hip hop combination.